<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lomorage Client on Lomorage Documentation</title><link>https://docs.lomorage.com/docs/Installation/lomorage-client/</link><description>Recent content in Lomorage Client on Lomorage Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://docs.lomorage.com/docs/Installation/lomorage-client/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>iOS</title><link>https://docs.lomorage.com/docs/Installation/lomorage-client/installation-ios/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.lomorage.com/docs/Installation/lomorage-client/installation-ios/</guid><description>Install Lomorage iOS client
#
You can install the application on either iPad or iPhone, the minimum iOS version required in 10.3.
--
After launching Lomorage, it should be able to discover the Lomorage service running in the same network. If you have multiple Lomorage service instances running, those will be listed and you can choose one to use. If Lomorage service can&amp;rsquo;t be discovered automatically, you can discover the service via QRCode Scanning when using Windows or MacOS LomoAgent (open settings in LomoAgent to show the QRCode), or you can input the IP address and port manually.</description></item><item><title>Andriod</title><link>https://docs.lomorage.com/docs/Installation/lomorage-client/installation-andriod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.lomorage.com/docs/Installation/lomorage-client/installation-andriod/</guid><description>Install Lomorage App in Android phone
#
Currently you can install the app on Android phone, the minimal version is 7.1.
Update history：：2021-08-07
#
Fix can not create log issue on android 11 Fix directory filter duplicate issue. Click below icon to go to Goole Play Store to download.
Directly download APK
--
After launching Lomorage, it will take a few minutes to import all your photos and videos on phone in the first time.</description></item><item><title>Web</title><link>https://docs.lomorage.com/docs/Installation/lomorage-client/installation-web/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.lomorage.com/docs/Installation/lomorage-client/installation-web/</guid><description>Install Lomorage Web client
#
You can use Lomorage Web client to upload photos/videos from desktop/laptop using browser, and you can use the gallery to view the photos/videos stored in Lomorage.
If you are using Lomorage Service in MacOS, then you can just click &amp;ldquo;import&amp;rdquo; menu item in LomoAgent Application, and it will open the web application.
If you are using Lomorage Service in Raspberry Pi, then you can use the following command to install Lomorage Web client on your raspberry Pi:</description></item></channel></rss>